

ROBERT COSTIN CIOBANU

Bucharest, Romania

Tel:+40723771793 / E-mail: ciobanurobert4@gmail.com

A reliable, punctual, confident person who excels working in a busy customer service environment. My passion for travel motivated me to complete different contracts around the world starting off in Dubai almost 7 years ago and moving on to the UK and Spain working for world renowned hospitality and entertainment venues. Followed recently by an amazing opportunity to work as a Bar Manager for the company Tatel Restaurants in Ibiza. Having just completed this I am now looking for a similar role in which allows me to travel and expand on my current knowledge and skills. I am already familiar with the very high standards of service and dynamic venues and feel I am now ready for a step which allows me to continue working in a vibrant hospitality environment.

LANGUAGES:

- ENGLISH FLUENT(WRITTEN/SPOKEN)
- SPANISH FLUENT(WRITTEN/SPOKEN)

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND:

- HOSPITALITY AND TOURISM (HOSPITALITY TECHNICIAN)

ECONOMIC COLLEGE HERMES, BUCHAREST, ROMANIA 2007-2012

RELATED WORK EXPERIENCE:

- TATEL RESTAURANTS, TATEL IBIZA IBIZA, SPAIN May 2019 October 2019 BAR MANAGER
- UNION STREET CAFE BY GORDON RAMSAY UNION STREET, LONDON October 2017 April 2019 ASSISTANT BAR MANAGER
- SURF LOUNGE IBIZA SANT ANTONI DE PORTMANY, IBIZA April 2017 September 2017 BARTENDER Promoted to BAR MANAGER
- SAVILL COURT HOTEL AND SPA ENGLEFIELD GREEN, SURREY, UK March 2014 April 2017 HEAD BARTENDER
- ARMANI HOTEL DUBAI Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Blvd, DUBAI December 2012 March 2014 -

BARTENDER

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPPON REQUEST